Guide to the Lindseth Collection of Alice Ephemera MSS.368
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series V: Printed Ephemera, 272637
  - Subseries C: Posters, 272767
    - Alice in Wonderland Posters, [Undated]; 272937 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Dimensions: 1. 12.5"x21". 2. 13"x18.5".
    - Alice in Wonderland Posters, [Undated]; 272938 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      1. Children's Theater of Portland presenting "Alice in the Wonderland of Pooh". Pickard Theater on the Bowdoin College campus. 2. Hollywood Bowl, color poster for 60th anniversary season, 1981, depicting a bright White Rabbit against the background of Hollywood.
      Dimensions: 1. 22"x14" 2. 22"x14".
    - Deaf Alice Poster, 1979; 272939 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      Dimensions: 12"x17"
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland RKO Film Poster Depicting Enlarged Tea Party, 1951; 272936 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Dimensions: 14"x36"
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Technicolor Posters, 1974; 272912 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      1. Alice and the Tweedles. 2. The White Rabbit. 3. The Queen of Hearts and the Cheshire Cat. 4. The Mad Hatter and the Tea Cup.
      Dimensions: 1. 11"x13". 2. 11"x13". 3. 11"x13". 4. 11"x13".
    - Large Alice in Wonderland posters, 278815 (Folder 1)
    - Japanese stage plays, 1998-2002 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 19)
    - Jan Švankmajer's Něco z Alenky, 1987 (Box Shared Fales 003, Folder 13)
    - Ulysse, Alice, Oh! Hisse exhibit, 1978 (Flat-file-folder [large folder])
    - Walt Disney presents Alice nel Paese delle Meraviglie, 1951; cuid6203 (Item MSS.368.cuid6203)
    - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland in emoji, Undated (Flat-file-folder [large folder])
    - Down the Rabbit Hole, Dartmouth College's 2007 Winter Carnival (Box Shared Fales 001, Folder 10)
- Oversize Series VII: Books/Magazines/Clippings/Newspapers, 272282
  - Subseries E: Activity Books, 272544
    - Alice in Wonderland; a Giant Coloring Book, 1963; 272545 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland; a Giant Coloring Book, [Undated]; 272552 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, [Undated]; 272551 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Colorful Alice in Wonderland Coloring Book, [Undated]; 272546 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Kim's Storybook Friends Coloring Book; Six Delightful Storybook Characters to Color, 1969; 272550 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Paper Doll Storybook Kiddles, 1981; 272364 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      6 dolls with stands and press out dresses and 6 storybook scenes to press out and set up. One of the dolls is Alice in WonderLiddle.
    - Stand-Ups; Adventures of Alice in Wonderland, [Undated]; 272366 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Sticker Fun; Stencil and Coloring Book, 1951; 272365 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries F: Newspapers, 272543
    - The London Times, [1865-1972]; 272283 (Box 25)
- Oversize Series VIII: Art, 272516
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 1/26, [Undated]; 272517 (Box 38, Item 1)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 1/26
    Description: Cover, Frontspiece, Bibliography.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 2/26, [Undated]; 272518 (Box 38, Item 2)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 2/26
    Description: Headpiece for Forward.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 3/26, [Undated]; 272519 (Box 38, Item 3)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 3/26
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 4/36, [Undated]; 272520 (Box 38, Item 4)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 4/26
    Description: Headpiece for Biography.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 5/26, [Undated]; 272521 (Box 38, Item 5)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 5/26
    Description: Headpiece for "Little Known Facts--".
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 6/26, [Undated]; 272522 (Box 38, Item 6)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 6/26
    Description: Headpiece for Introduction.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 7/26, [Undated]; 272523 (Box 38, Item 7)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 7/26
    Description: Alice sat nodding sleepily on a mossy bank beside her big sister, who was reading.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 8/36, [Undated]; 272524 (Box 38, Item 8)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 8/26
    Description: Crocodile: Danger from pirates, or robbers, or deceitful creditors.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 9/26, [Undated]; 272525 (Box 38, Item 9)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 9/26
    Description: Looking-Glass: Mirror; for a girl - she is jilted at the church door.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 10/26, [Undated]; 272526 (Box 38, Item 10)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 10/26
    Description: Wood: If you dream that you are walking along in an extensive wood, it denotes that you will quickly fall in love and also that you will be often married.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 11/26, [Undated]; 272527 (Box 38, Item 11)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 11/26
    Description: Caterpillar: You will soon witness some marvelous spiritual phenomena.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 12/26, [Undated]; 272528 (Box 38, Item 12)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 12/26
    Description: Nest: bird's nest; for a young woman, this dream foretells a change of abode.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 13/26, [Undated]; 272529 (Box 38, Item 13)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 13/26
    Description: Frog: Neglect, lack of interest in your work, slovenliness in dress and in manner.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 14/26, [Undated]; 272530 (Box 38, Item 14)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 14/26
    Description: Whistling: Gives prediction of a sensational fire, or storm within a week from now.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 15/26, [Undated]; 272531 (Box 38, Item 15)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 15/26
    Description: Baby: To dream you had to take a baby, is a hint to fulfill the dream at your earliest possible convenience.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 16/26, [Undated]; 272532 (Box 38, Item 16)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 16/26
    Description: Treacle: Beware of excessive heat.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 17/26, [Undated]; 272533 (Box 38, Item 17)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 17/26
    Description: Tea: To sip or drink tea, gives promise that you will yet secure the secret of long life, that you may live one hundred years or more.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 18/26, [Undated]; 272534 (Box 38, Item 18)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 18/26
    Description: Procession: You shall be the gainer or guardian of property; you shall be the parent of a son who will be an illustrious warrior. He will cause pain, but will be a mighty noble.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 19/26, [Undated]; 272535 (Box 38, Item 19)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 19/26
    Description: Club: To dream of a club, denotes short imprisonment which will bring you no disgrace. You will only save money.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 20/26, [Undated]; 272536 (Box 38, Item 20)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 20/26
    Description: Game: To dream of playing ball denotes you will be seized for gambling.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 21/26, [Undated]; 272537 (Box 38, Item 21)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 21/26
    Description: Reading: To dream of reading, denotes a pleasure trip on which you will get secret information about a plan which will yield you prosperity.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 22/26, [Undated]; 272538 (Box 38, Item 22)
    Description: Shoes: Practical jokes and unwise, harsh criticism alienate your dearest friends from you.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 23/26, [Undated]; 272539 (Box 38, Item 23)
    Title: Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 22/26
    Description: Inkstand: Avoid Hot drinks; otherwise, you will be troubled with debility or weakness, loss of appetite, indigestion and many other diseases arising from a deranged condition of the stomach.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 24/26, [Undated]; 272540 (Box 38, Item 24)
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 25/26, [Undated]; 272541 (Box 38, Item 25)
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 26/26, [Undated]; 272542 (Box 38, Item 26)
  - Malice in Wonderland -- Julie Inman, 1980 (Flat-file-folder [large folder])